{
    "id": "a7de84aae5e841949e307e418a620cad",
    "title": "Until, before and after",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "29e0ae58fc8241339888eaa279599b51",
            "title": "Until, Before, And After",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He won’t marry ................. he gets a job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "before",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don’t open the window .................. the rain stops.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "after",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will wait here .................. you finish your work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "before",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don’t go ..................... I tell you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "after",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We will have to live in this house ................... we find a better one.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "before",
                        "after",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He had locked the door ................. he went out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "before",
                        "after",
                        "until"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You must wash your hands ..................... you eat anything.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "before",
                        "until",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He will finish his work ............... he goes home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "before",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He had counted the coins ..................... he put them in the box.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "before",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He went out to play ....................... he did his homework.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "after",
                        "until",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I put on my clothes ........................ I had washed myself.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "before",
                        "until",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We reached the station ten minutes ....................... the train left.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "until",
                        "after",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}